Guide to the Advisory Committee on the Status of Women records, 1970-2006.
Advisory Committee on the Status of Women records, 1970-2006
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Advisory Committee on the Status of Women records, 1970-2006.
53/26/3595
Advisory Committee on the Status of Women.
2 cubic feet
Correspondence, Reports, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, reports, and subject files.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1972, Title IX of the Education Amendments decreed that educational institutions that receive federal financial assistance must eliminate gender biases in education. That same three of its faculty members, Alice Cook, Jennie Farley, and Gail McCall founded the Provost's Ad Hoc Committee on the Status of Women. This ad hoc group was eventually made permanent at Cornell University and renamed the Advisory Committee on the Status of Women (ACSW).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, reports, and subject files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Advisory Committee on the Status of Women.; Cook, Alice Hanson.; Farley, Jennie T.; McCall, Gail.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University.Provost's Ad Hoc Committee on the Status of Women.
Subjects:
Sex discrimination in education.; Women college teachers--New York (N.Y.); Women--Education.; Women--Employment.; Women--Legal status, laws, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, and Related Materials
  - Provost Plan Re: suggestions to improve the status of women at Cornell, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - From Karen Feeny Re: Women’s Action Council and suggestions to Cornell, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - From Karen Feeny Re: family nepotism and “he” pronoun use in Grad School App., 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - From Dept. of English Re: part‐time employment proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - D.R. Corson Re: Chronicle article, family nepotism rule and fringe benefits, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - From Richard Horch Re: Female Staff and Admin. Employees Survey, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - From Margaret Gaffney Re: Discussions with women staff and faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Provost Plane Re: Revised Statement of Purpose and members list, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - V. Provost Risley Re: seeking information about university job positions, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Re: Cornell University Employee Survey Responses, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - V. Provost Risley Re: Chronicle article and Committee Recommendations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - From Peg Condon Re: Financial Aid for Transfer Students, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Dr. Gurowitz Re: Questions for Division of Campus Life, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Library Compensation Study, Recommendations and Research, Ad Hoc Trustee Committee on the Status of Women Report, 1973-07-1974-05 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and activities, Recommendations to Provost, Provost’s 1st Annual Progress Report on the Status of Women by date, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and activities, Recommendations to Provost, Provost’s 2nd Annual Progress Report on the Status of Women, Annual Reports of the Committee by date, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and activities, Summary of Recommendations since 1972, Provost’s 3rd Annual Progress Report on the Status of Women, Annual Reports of the Committee by date, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and activities, Provost’s 4th Annual Progress Report on the Status of Women, Annual Reports of the Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Employment Subcommittee, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACSW Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, and Reports by date, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Including the Provost’s 5th Annual Progress Report on the Status of Women
  - Academic Employment Subcommittee, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Faculty Re: Discriminatory Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - William Wendt Re: Blue Light Bus service, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Re: Title IX Intercollegiate Athletics Issues, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Employee Newsletter Re: ACSW Background, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Statler Club Re: Exclusion of non‐exempt staff, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Alfred Fittipaldi Re: Nonsexist Language in Job Titles, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - William Herbster Re: Advertising Summer Mgt Training Programs to women, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Employee Benefit Programs: Pregnancy Health Questions, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Research, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Non‐Academic Employment Study Draft, 1979-10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Women’s Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Daycare Subcommittee, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action Advisory Board, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Admissions, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Health Services, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Physical Education and Athletics, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Compliance Review, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report - Academic Employment, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Meeting minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - From Patricia Carry Stewart Re: Request Annual Report for Women Trustees, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Re: Sex Discrimination Conference Sponsorship, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - From Keith Kennedy Re: Assoc. Provost for Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Gary Posner Re: Personnel Policy #705 Question, review of personal files, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - W. Donald Cooke Re: one‐year appointments for permanent women staff, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Dorothy Pasternack Re: Women at Cornell in Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Keith Kennedy Re: Harvard Women Faculty Hires, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Alison Cassaret Re: No women nominated for General Committee of Grad School, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Committee Organization, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Academic Employment, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Non‐Academic Employment, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Restructure of Subcommittees Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - William Bushaw Re: Questions about student loans, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Background on the Committee for New Members, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Follow‐ups to women attending the Board of Trustees meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - William Herbster Re: Women’s Soccer and Media coverage of Women’s Sports, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Director of Personnel Search, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Constance E. Cook petition for access to the University, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sexual Harassment Subcommittee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Maternity Leave/Day Care, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Programs - Appearances at Women Student Groups, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Programs - Dispute Settlement Workshop Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Programs - ILR Women in Management Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Major Activities of The Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Sexual Harassment, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Title IX Subcommittee on Athletics, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Committee on Academic Employment, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Subcommittee on Non‐Academic Employment, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Subcommittee of Family Issues, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Ronald Brieger Re: Sociology Search Committee should seek a woman, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Provost Kennedy Re: external search for VP Research to include women, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Don Johnson Re: Sexual Harassment Report, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Don Johnson and Provost Kennedy: budget cuts and layoffs, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Michael Buthe Re: Secretaries Day flyer offensive to women, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Nancy Hicks Re: New Health Insurance concerns for women, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - FCR resolution to include diversity statement, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Provost Kennedy Re: restructure of PASCOW, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Jansen Noyes Re: Male pronoun use in University Bylaws, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Mary Purcell Visit, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Panel Discussion on Interviewing for Academic Positions, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Women Faculty Reception, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Administrative Managers Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs - Sexual Harassment: Prevention and Resolution, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Major Activities of The Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Academic Employment Subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Sexual Harassment, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Daycare Subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Athletics Subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Day Care Subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Subcommittee on Athletics, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Academic Employment Subcommittee, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Letters to members, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Status of Women Report circulation, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee Reorganization, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Alice Cook Re: Lifelong Membership, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - ACSW Information Sheet for Women’s Fair, 1985-03-08 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Affirmative Action in Hiring Memo, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Re: Women’s Development Fund and unfair application procedures, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Re: Potential Board of Trustees meeting with Faculty Women, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee Reorganization, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Goals, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - ACSW Accomplishments, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Purpose, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Activities of the Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Affirmative Action, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Personnel, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Sexual Harassment and Safety, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Ad Hoc Taskforce on the Status of Women & Minorities, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report - Evaluations Report, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Report on the Status of Women and Minorities Review Team Final Report, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - From Joseph Bugliari Re: Faculty Education Programs on Management, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Joan Brumberg Re: Women’s Studies presentation to the Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Paul Eshelman Re: Personal Computer Work Settings at Cornell Survey, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Harassment Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Meeting minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Catherine Murray‐Rust Re: Lifelong Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - From ILR Extension, Flyer for Women Managers’ Forum, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - From Joan Egner: University Connections Recommendations, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Women’s Report, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Childcare, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Proposal for New Information Subcommittee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ACSW Reunion (includes former members list), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - ACSW Report, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - Sexual Harassment Subcommittee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - Subcommittee on Support Services (Childcare), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - Comparable Worth Research, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - Personnel Subcommittee (Computers in the Workplace), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report - Career Development/ Dual Career Subcommittee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Non‐Academic Employment Subcommittee, 1976-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - From Jocelyn Hart Re: Report on Sexual Harassment Complaint Procedures, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Re: Luncheon with Trustee women and bios, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Teagle Women’s Locker room Expansion, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gender Research, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Events - Impact of Sexual Harassment on the Academic Community, Molly Hite presenter, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Events - Conference on Women and Science, ILR Extension Coordinating Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report - Committee Activities, including luncheon with women trustees/council members, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report - Subcommittee on Family Support Services, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report - Child Care Subcommittee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report - Information Subcommittee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - From Roz Kenworthy Re: Problems for single‐mother students, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Jocelyn Hart Re: Orientation Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Re: Women’s Professional Network, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - From Joseph Ballantyne Re: more women desired for Research Council, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Re: FCR Resolution/ University Affirmative Action Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Re: University Transportation/ Parking Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Provost Barker Re: VP for Research and Advanced Studies search, seek a woman, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Displaced Homemakers Canter Re: Petition to honor Alice Cook at anniversary, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Advisory Committee on the Status of Minorities Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gender Research, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretaries Day, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Events - Eleanor Smeal (former NOW president) visit to Cornell, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Events - Jane Crawford presentation: Double standards in Language, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Events - Alison Casarett and Jennie Farley: Progress of Women, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report - Activities of the Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report - Work and Family Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report - Professional Development Subcommittee, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Committee Business (membership, planning and schedules), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gender Research, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Women and Addiction, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - ACSW Efforts: Equal Pay, Equal Opportunity, Quality of Life, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Women in the Workplace Subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Women and Addictions subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Campus Climate Subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report - Employment Subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - From Jocelyn Hart Re: ACSW Annual Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Office of Transportation Services Re: Transit Map offensive to women, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Alan Lentini Re: New OHR Liaison to ACSW, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Research, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Employment Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Harassment Report, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Campus Climate Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Work and Family Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ACSW History, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Re: ACSW Annual Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Judith Monson, PCCW Re: Communication between women’s groups, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - From President Rhodes Re: Classification Review, compensation and family issues, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - VP Human Resources Search Committee Re: candidates should support women, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Dr. Chastillo‐Chavez Re: Offer to Support FCR Committee on Affirmative Action, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - From PCCW Re: Invitation to Dinner, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - John Ford, Dean of Students Re: Welcome and Introduction to ACSW, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gender Research, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Campus Climate/ Power Sharing Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Harassment Report, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Events - Richard Hurd: University Women Employees and Unionization, ILR Extension, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Events - Brown Bag Lunch, Panel Discussion on the Status of Women at Cornell, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Events - Andrea Parrot and Nina Cummings: Sexual Harassment and Acquaintance Rape, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Events - Forum on the Nature of Academic Appointments at Cornell, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations from members, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - External Committee Evaluation, Human Services Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - Revised Statement of Purpose and Organization Plan, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - Campus Climate Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - Employment Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report - Work and Family Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - FCR Committee on Affirmative Action Report, 1991‐2, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - John Wiesenfeld Re: Strategic Planning Advisory Board needs women representation, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - From Susan Marash Re: CHRISP campus‐wide job information, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Pamela Calla Re: breastfeeding at Day Hall incident, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - President Rhodes Re” Issues for Conversation at Spring Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - From Sr VP Morley and Provost Re: Classification Review Study Results, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Cornell Chronicle Re: Statler Club Exclusionary Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gender Research, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PCCW Information, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mentoring, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sexual Harassment Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Mary Katzenstein: Influence of women in the Presidential Election, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Panel Discussion, Progress Towards Diversity Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Sexual Assault Awareness and Prevention Week, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Eloy Rodriguez: Chicanos/Latinos in Science Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Informational Session about ACSW, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events - Dr. Phyllis Moen: A Life Course Approach to Life, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 20th Anniversary and Cook Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations from members, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report - ACSW Goals and Accomplishments: Long‐range and 92‐93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report - Campus Climate Subcommittee, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report - Employment Subcommittee, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Employment Subcommittees, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Work/Life Subcommittee, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - From New Women’s Network Re: Appeals Process for Compensation Research Study, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Martha Eller Re: PCCW Women’s Research grants applications, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Re: 1994 Summer Session Theme, “Women’s Lives”, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Membership Applications - Re: member Susan Marash, updates on health, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Re: suggestions for Presidential Search Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gender Research, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Campus Climate Subcommittee, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sexual Harassment Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Women’s Studies Fall Colloquium Series, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Deborah Homsher: “From Blood to Verdict, Three Women on Trial”, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Andrea Parrot: Women’s Health Issues, Optimizing your health, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events - Alice Cook 90th Birthday Celebration, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)